The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
This restriction... isn't bad.
Junior was saved by Teacher a long time ago.
She taught me alchemy and cultivation.
Now that she's in trouble,
Junior needs to help her.
This gate connects to Teacher's secret room.
No one knows about it.
Junior will guard you.
If something is wrong, I will tell Senior.
Senior !
Senior, are you hurt ?
I'm fine.
With the talisman,
we can borrow the Heaven Stealing Furnace's energy.
Yes.
The Heaven Stealing Furnace
was built by the Founder in the early days of the sect.
For thousands of years,
it has accumulated a huge amount of spiritual energy.
Each refinement
makes it stronger.
You can say that
it's stealing the heavens.
Now that we also have the talisman,
once they start refining a pill
we will use it
to steal their spiritual energy
and open the pill seal.
Is this furnace also part of the Heaven Stealing Furnace ?
Not really.
I built this pill furnace in secret after studying the main one.
I was planning to use it as my last trump card.
If the Sect were to do something to me,
I would use this furnace
to turn the main furnace to dust.
Since the Elders would've been busy repairing the furnace,
they wouldn't have been able to track me down.
After we undo the pill seal,
will the spiritual energy remain in the furnace ?
Yes.
Then if I cultivate in this furnace,
wouldn't it help my breakthrough ?
Fellow cultivators,
I know that your precious grade 4 pills
were difficult to obtain.
You cannot bear to part with them.
Senior Ouyang,
we don't mind parting with our pills.
I just want to ask you
if you can guarantee that by sacrificing our grade 4 pills,
we will be able to refine a grade 5 pill ?
Don't underestimate alchemy.
What is there to guarantee ?
Are you worried for my pill !?
Listen up,
the Pill Sacrifice
can indeed increase the success rate of refinement.
Alchemy is to refine the spirit of heaven and earth.
Now do what's right !
This grade 5 pill will shock the world.
In the future, I will make a grade 6...
No, even a grade 7 pill !
Don't you want
to follow this old man on this journey ?
We are willing.
The time of Yin has come.
Note: Yin = night, Yang = day
Everyone,
open the furnace !
Pill Sacrifice !
It's starting.
First sacrifice, grade 4 Demon Blood Pill !
It's really working !
This alchemy technique is really advanced.
Ouyang Zi is an alchemy genius.
He created the Pill Sacrifice method.
By sacrificing lower-level pills
it can increase the success rate of refining higher-level pills
Second sacrifice, grade 4 Nature Gathering Pill !
Another sacrifice, grade 4 Cloud Stirring Pill !
Grade 4 Heaven and Earth Pill !
Golden Clouds Pill !
Senior, this is a grade 7 Cyan Cloud Pill !
After using the Pill Sacrifice,
how can there be so little spiritual energy ?
Forget it,
even if I need to use the Heaven Stealing Formation,
I will make sure my pill succeeds !
This is bad, they will find the secret room.
Senior, don't move.
Wan'er will take care of this.
The Ancestors ordered...
I will help Senior Ouyang.
Are you sure you want to stop me ?
No !
This cannot be happening to me !
I will help you, Senior Ouyang.
That's very kind of you.
Senior's cultivation is profound,
you should control the flow of spiritual energy.
Let Junior handle the Heaven Stealing Furnace.
Okay.
This vortex of energy is extremely violent.
Even a Nascent Soul would have trouble absorbing it.
This should compensate how much we are stealing.
I've done it !
My own grade 5 pill is taking shape !
Senior,
you will need to rely on yourself now.
Original body, appear !
Sun Zhenwei ?
What are you plotting ?
Elder Li, the ceremony is in a few days.
Even without makeup,
you need to try your wedding dress.
It will be troublesome if it doesn't fit you.
Senior has been in seclusion for a few days...
I wonder if it's going well.
You're so ungrateful !
Don't test my patience.
What was your apprentice's name again ?
Oh, right.
Zhou Lin.
He's very loyal to you.
What did you do ?
He's not very smart.
That day, your apprentice was acting suspiciously.
And you never helped Ouyang Zi before.
I asked him about it
but he was shameless.
He chose death over having his soul searched.
So I had to fulfill his wish.
How dare you !
This is the Cloud Sky Sect,
it doesn't matter if I kill him.
It doesn't matter if I kill you either.
I advise you to stay put.
Whether you obey me or not,
it all depends on you.
I'm sorry, Teacher troubled you.
The Nascent Soul Embryo is forming,
I just need to keep injecting spiritual energy into it.
Come back !
The Ji Realm is preventing me from reaching Nascent Soul again.
Wow, the Cloud Sky Sect is so luxurious !
I heard Elder Li is very beautiful.
Please come in.
Please.
Congratulations !
Brother Liu, how are you ?
Tianyi Zhenren
Luoyue Sect Leader
Middle stage Nascent Soul
The number one Sect in the country of Chu
really impresses me.
I wonder when we can share our knowledge.
It's just a matter of reputation.
Liu Fei
Cloud Sky Sect Leader
Middle stage Nascent Soul
There are hermits with higher cultivation than mine,
way more talented than me.
So there are other Ancestors in the Cloud Sky Sect ?
Please.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations fellow cultivator Sun.
Please come in.
Greetings, Tianyi Zhenren.
Is this the groom ?
You really are Lingwu's son,
a handsome talented man.
You're flattering me.
Go on.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I advise you to be obedient.
Otherwise, someone else you know might get hurt again.
Congratulations fellow cultivator Sun.
Thank you, thank you.
Please,
both of you come in.
What an ideal couple !
Thank you. thank you.
Senior...
Fellow cultivators, long time no see.
We must drink today to celebrate.
It's time !
It's really a perfect match.
A cultivator with a grade 5 achemist,
it's only a matter of time before he reaches Nascent Soul.
This Zhenwei couple is truly beautiful.
This kid is lucky !
What an ideal couple,
they're perfect for each other.
Today is the day of your Dual Cultivation ceremony.
It's a happy day for our Cloud Sky Sect !
I wish you two a happy marriage,
may you live happily ever after.
We cultivators,
don't go through every mortal rite.
After you drink this cup of wine,
consider the ceremony to be complete.
Don't mess with me now.
What's going on ?
Senior !
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.